("God Only Knows"
by The Beach Boys)
♪♪♪
♪ I may not always love you ♪
♪ But long as there
are stars above you ♪
♪ You never need to doubt it ♪
♪ I'll make you
so sure about it ♪
♪ God only knows what
I'd be without you ♪
♪ If you should ever leave me ♪
♪ Though life would
still go on believe me ♪
♪ The world could
show nothing to me ♪
♪ So what good
would living do me ♪
♪ God only knows what
I'd be without you ♪
♪♪♪
♪ [Vocalizing] ♪
♪ God only knows what
I'd be without you ♪
♪ If you should ever leave me ♪
♪ Well life would still
go on believe me ♪
♪ The world could
show nothing to me ♪
♪ So what good
would living do me ♪
♪ God only knows what
I'd be without you ♪
♪ God only knows ♪
♪ God only knows what
I'd be without you ♪
♪ God only knows ♪
♪ God only knows what
I'd be without you ♪
♪ God only knows ♪
♪ God only knows what
I'd be without you ♪
♪ God only knows ♪
♪ God only knows what
I'd be without you ♪
(waves lapping)